Contact Information

- 0424 182 450
- 8 Jib Court Mermaid Waters, QLD 4218
- asantidrian83@gmail.com
- in <u>Linkedin</u>
- Github Github

Technical Skills

- Platforms
 - MS Windows (98, 2000, NT, XP, 2003, VISTA, 7)
 - TSO
- Languages
 - JavaScript
 - Node.js
 - Express.js
 - HTML/CSS
 - Bootstrap
 - jQuery
 - Cobol/CICS
 - SQL

Alicia Santidrian

Objective

I am interested in gaining experience in a company where I can develop my skills, acquire new expertise and build my career through my hard work. I am open to any opportunity given as I have almost completed and 6 months intensive coding course and I could not be more motivated to get back to a programming role.

Work Experience

Immediately after my arrival in Australia in October 2012, I started a 12 months English course to acquire a professional level of English to be able to incorporate into a working environment in Australia.

From 2013 until the commence in my current job I worked as a Physics and a Mathematics private tutor for year 12- and first-year university science students. During that period of time, I also worked as an administrative assistant for an international student agency.

Once I obtained a visa without work hours restrictions, I began working full time in the current company where I am still working up to date.

Orders Administrator/Sales

March 2018 - Current

Australian Caravan Centre

Gold Coast, Australia

My main role in Australian Caravan Centre entails:

- Liaising with the factory to place all customer orders.
- Liaising with the customers and advising them on the customisation of their new caravan. Providing information regarding all the technical queries they may have.
- Keeping all the customer date up to date through the Eclipse DMS
- Sales consultant of all the extras and /or accessories available to purchase for each customer's caravan.
- Handover coordinator. Organizing the transport of the caravan from the factory to the Dealership and contacting customer to arrange the handover appointment.
- Filling temporally other roles vacancies while needed, such as warranty and service clerk
- Carrying out any requested task that was needed outside my main role.

Skills

- Time Management
- Meeting Targets and Deadlines on Schedule
- Multi-tasking
- Communication and Negotiation
- Quick Learner
- Working and Integrating into Teams

Experience

- Data Base
- Teaching experience
- Application and System Analysis
- Banking industry
- Supporting Project Management
- Business Strategy
- Application Development,
 Testing and Implementation
- Developing Technical Specifications and Documentation of Processes
- Customer Service
- Sales

Analyst/Programmer

Nov 2010 - Sep 2012

Everis Group

Madrid, Spain

Everis is a multi-national consulting firm originating from Madrid Spain that provides business strategy, IT solutions, application development, and outsourcing services.

My role as an analyst programmer for Everis Group entailed:

- Developing, testing, and implementing new applications.
- Worked on various projects, the longest for Banco Popular for developing and implementing an application for trading in foreign currency.
- Learning and completing the entire application development process from functional analysis through to client delivery
- Working across departments and teams helping coordinate communication and negotiations.
- Writing code and testing on various programs in test and production environment and prior to the application integration
- Providing detailed documentation for the entire process.

Project Management Junior Assistant Oct 2008 - June 2009

Vodafone Spain

Madrid, Spain

I worked for Vodafone Spain in their Technology area, more specifically in their planning and demand management department. This department was responsible for managing the operational plan of project investments across systems, products and services. My role as a junior assistant for Vodafone entailed:

- Technical and administrative tasks to support project managers responsible for submitting project investment approvals to the committee
- Improvements on tool architecture used for managing the operational plan.
- Automating the monitoring reports of the operational plan
- Performing data entry for multiple projects involving business cases, systems analysis, and project planning.

Education

The Coding Boot Camp at the University of Sydney, in collaboration with Trilogy Education Services.

University of Sydney

2022

Licenciate Degree of Physics Science

Universisdad Complutense de Madrid (UCM), Complutense University of Madrid

2010

Languages

- Spanish *Native Language*
- English *Proficient*
- French *Basic*

References

National Manager

Matt Mackinnon

Australian Caravan Centre

matt@australiancaravancentre.com.au

Supervisor while working at Everis

Raul Canto Luna PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC) Senior Analyst

Raul.canto.luna@gmail.com